<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Tim Pittman</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Tim Pittman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#39;https://twitter.com/pittman021&#39;&gt;pittman021&lt;/a&gt;.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2019 15:03:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Setup a Hugo Blog with Netlify CMS</title>
      <link>/posts/how-to-setup-a-hugo-blog-with-netlify-cms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2019 15:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/how-to-setup-a-hugo-blog-with-netlify-cms/</guid>
      <description>This is how you create a Hugo static site and install Netlify CMS. Netlify CMS is a free open-source tool for managing your content. You get setup with an /admin section of your site to write, edit, and publish your blog articles.
I wanted to write this because I came across several gotchas that slowed me down, such as installing and updating a theme as well as configuring my Netlify site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Simple Writing Tool</title>
      <link>/posts/creating-a-simple-writing-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 21:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/creating-a-simple-writing-tool/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this year I came across a book titled The Artist&amp;rsquo;s Way. This book outlines a journaling habit and other activities that are intended to unlock your creativity. It calls for writing by hand 750 words each day for a month. You freewrite without stopping &amp;amp; throw away the draft when you&amp;rsquo;re done.
I decided to pick this habit to develop a productive morning routine &amp;amp; keep my head clear and remain focused.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customer Success as Product Management</title>
      <link>/posts/customer-success-as-product-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 23:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/customer-success-as-product-management/</guid>
      <description>Product Managers know the importance of customer feedback to iterate and plan a product roadmap. But as a former CSM and team lead, I experienced first hand the huge opportunity lost in not leveraging CSMs as a source of customer &amp;amp; product feedback.
Consider that your team of 3 or 4 CSMs each may have 20-50 clients in their portfolio. That means on any given week they may be speaking with, as a whole, 20+ customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Up From Slavery by Booker T Washington</title>
      <link>/posts/up-from-slavery-by-booker-t-washington/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 15:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/up-from-slavery-by-booker-t-washington/</guid>
      <description>I love this book.
I gained as much from this book as I had from the past three. His writing is simple. He’s impactful and magnetic. He explains topics such as education, work ethic, race relations, reading and studying, opportunity, self-improvement, and meritocracy. It’s inspirational and wise - perhaps the single best book on the topic of success I’ve read.
He rose from being born in slavery to an honorary Harvard Ph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of 5 Product Onboardings</title>
      <link>/posts/review-of-5-product-onboardings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 15:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/review-of-5-product-onboardings/</guid>
      <description>At Sumo we’ve recently discussed customer onboarding. As an exercise I reviewed 5-10 product’s and reviewed their onboarding experiences.
I wanted to share my findings on 5 of those.
Contents
Good Product Onboarding Scoring Reviews CustomerIO Drip Hubspot CRM Intercom Klaviyo Final Scores Summary &amp;amp; Takeaways
Good Product Onboarding Good onboarding is a function of good customer experience. So what is customer experience?
How customers perceive their interactions with your company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Coaching Habit by Michael Bungay Stanier</title>
      <link>/posts/the-coaching-habit-by-michael-bungay-stanier/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 15:24:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-coaching-habit-by-michael-bungay-stanier/</guid>
      <description>Tell less and ask more. Your advice is not as good As you think it is. Michael Bungay Stanier
 I finished this book in the middle of last year. I haven’t read a lot of books on this topic — but this was the most impactful thus far. It provides you the mindset required to be an effective leader and coach of people. It tackles the issues many managers face — creating overdependence, getting overwhelmed and becoming disconnected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Momentum</title>
      <link>/posts/get-momentum/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 15:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/get-momentum/</guid>
      <description>In 2017 I taught myself to code.
I continued to read articles about courses to help learn full-stack development. As a Project Manager at the time, it was immediately helpful to understand the web and communicate with developers.
I took freecodecamp.com. I learned JavaScript and completed front-end (react) courses. I recommend this fully to anyone working in SaaS or technology. It’s the language of the web. The magic of the internet become something tangible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shipping Gardenshq.com</title>
      <link>/posts/shipping-gardenshq-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 20:53:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/shipping-gardenshq-com/</guid>
      <description>I’ve shipped my latest side project, gardenshq.com, a personal CRM geared around gift giving.
This idea came from my girlfriend who was storing all her contacts and gifts in a google sheet, with no easy way to be 1) notified of upcoming dates 2) saving gifts she found around the web and 3) organizing gifts around holidays and birthdays. She’s a power gifter and she something with more oomph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning JavaScript: Lessons</title>
      <link>/posts/learning-javascript-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 20:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/learning-javascript-lessons/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this I decided to learn JavaScript. Here’s what I’ve learned thus far.
Background:
I ran into an article by Derek Sivers on learning how to program: https://sivers.org/prog.
Then his follow-up article on learning JavaScript. https://sivers.org/learn-js
After running through FreeCodeCamp’s HTML/CSS courses, these articles inspired me to tackle JavaScript. I figured it’d be fun to learn, help me in my current job, and had little downside.
Learning JavaScript
I started with Head First HTML5 Programming.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>